stlucianewsonline.com 2019-07-08

# Privacy Policy - StLuciaNewsOnline.com - St. Lucia News Online

Thank you for visiting StLuciaNewsOnline.com, a subsidiary of Andrews Media Services Corporation. Your privacy is important to us.

To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this web site.

 **The Information We Collect**

At this site, you can purchase advertising packages, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, and participate in one of our online forums or communities. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.

At certain parts of our site, only persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable information will be able to order products, programs, and services or otherwise participate in the site’s activities and offerings.

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows ’95 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your internet service provider (e.g. FLOW, Digicel, America Online).

 **How We Use The Information**

The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services.

If you choose to submit content for publication (e.g., a “letter to our editors”), we may publish your screen name and other information you have provided to us. We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services. We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request.

Agents and contractors of Andrews Media Services Corporation, who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Andrews Media Services Corporation.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice.

Finally, this web site will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.

 **Our Commitment to Security**

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.

 **How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about Andrews Media Services Corporation’s online policy for this site or its implementation you may contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#11707f75637466627c74757870727e636151767c70787d3f727e7c).

(1)(3)
